<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="79">
    <author>Pascal Kautz</author>
    <version>1.0.0.2</version>
    <title>
        <en>Platform Trailer With Crane</en>
		
        <nl>Platform Oplegger Met Kraan</nl>
		   
        <fr>Semi-Remorque A Plateforme Avec Grue</fr>
		   
        <de>Plattformauflieger Mit Kran</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[The Lizard platform trailer is a conventient trailer because of it's crane. 
The crane excludes the need of a forklift and can be used in practically every situation.

The hook can be used to pick up bigbags. 
This trailer also comes with a palletfork wich can be attached to the hook.

Hydraulic Clamp is an accessory for the crane of the platform trailer.
The hydraulic clamp can also be used to pick up bales.

Price:
- Trailer: 58.000$
- Palletfork: 2.000$
- Hydraulic Clamp:  2.000$

ChangeLog 1.0.0.2:
- Added semi-trailer without crane
- Added Hydraulic Clamp]]></en> 
        <nl><![CDATA[De platformoplegger is een handige oplegger door zijn kraan.
De kraan maakt de noodzaak van een vorkheftruck overbodig en kan in vrijwel elke situatie worden gebruikt.

De haak kan worden gebruikt voor het oppakken van bigbags.
Deze aanhanger wordt tevens geleverd met een palletvork die aan de haak kan worden bevestigd.

Hydraulische Klem is een hulpstuk voor de kraan van de plateau oplegger.
De hydraulische klem kan ook gebruikt worden om balen op te pakken.

Prijs:
- Oplegger: 58.000€
- Palletvork: 2.000€
- Hydraulische klem: 2.000€

ChangeLog 1.0.0.2:
- Oplegger zonder kraan toegevoegd
- Hydraulische klem toegevoegd]]></nl>	   
        <fr><![CDATA[La Lizard remorque plateforme est une remorque maniable grâce à sa grue.
La grue élimine le besoin d’un chariot élévateur et peut être utilisée dans presque toutes les situations.

Le crochet peut être utilisé pour ramasser des big bag.
Cette remorque est également livrée avec une fourche à palette qui peut être fixée au crochet.

La pince hydraulique est un accessoire pour la grue de la remorque à plateforme.
La pince hydraulique peut également être utilisée pour ramasser des balles.

Prix:
- Semi-remorque : 58.000 €
- Fourche à palettes : 2.000€
- Hydraulische klem: 2.000€
- Pince hydraulique: 2.000€

ChangeLog 1.0.0.2: 
- Ajout d'une semi-remorque sans grue
- Ajout la pince hydraulique]]></fr>   
        <de><![CDATA[Der Lizard Plattformauflieger ist aufgrund seines Krans ein handlicher auflieger.
Der Kran macht einen Gabelstapler überflüssig und kann in nahezu jeder Situation eingesetzt werden.

Der Haken kann zum Aufnehmen von Big Bags verwendet werden.
Zu diesem Anhänger gehört auch eine Palettengabel, die am Haken befestigt werden kann.

Die hydraulische Klemme ist ein Zubehör für den Kran des Plattformanhängers.
Die hydraulische Zange kann auch zum Aufnehmen von Ballen verwendet werden.

Preis:
- Auflieger: 58.000€
- Palettengabel: 2.000€
- Hydraulische Klemme: 2.000€

ChangeLog 1.0.0.2:
- Sattelauflieger ohne Kran hinzugefügt
- Hydraulische Klemme hinzugefügt]]></de>
    </description>
	
    <iconFilename>icon_platformTrailer.png</iconFilename>
	
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

	<l10n>
		<text name="Lizard_green">
			<en>Lizard Green</en>
			<de>Lizard Grün </de>
			<fr>Lizard Vert</fr>
			<nl>Lizard Groen</nl>
		</text>		
		<text name="Lizard_yellow">
			<en>Lizard Yellow</en>
			<de>Lizard Gelb </de>
			<fr>Lizard Jaune</fr>
			<nl>Lizard Geel</nl>
		</text>	
		<text name="action_openSides">
			<en>Open Sides</en>
			<de>Seiten Öffnen</de>
			<fr>Ouvrir Les Côtés</fr>
			<nl>Zijkanten Openen</nl>
		</text>	
		<text name="action_closeSides">
			<en>Close Sides</en>
			<de>Seiten Schließen</de>
			<fr>Fermer Les Côtés</fr>
			<nl>Zijkanten Sluiten</nl>
		</text>
		<text name="shopItem_hydraulicClamp">
			<en>Hydraulic Clamp</en>
			<de>Hydraulische Klemme</de>	
			<fr>Pince Hydraulique</fr>		
			<nl>Hydraulische Klem</nl>
		</text>		
	</l10n>
	
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="platformTrailer.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="platformTrailer02.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="craneFork.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="hydraulicClamp.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
</modDesc>
